

ABOUT ME

I am a Junior Full Stack Developer with experience in web technologies such as HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript, and advanced proficiency in frameworks and libraries like React and Node.js. I have knowledge in SQL databases and backend implementation TypeScript.

CONTACT

1

678567628

annahico@gmail.com

0

Barcelona Ciudad

GitHub

LinkedIn

STAKS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JAVASCRIPT
- GIT
- TYPESCRIPT
- NODE.JS
- REACT
- MYSQL
- EXPRESS
- GITHUB
- BOOTSTRAP

LANGUAGES

- Catalan Native
- Spanish Native
- English C2
- German A2



HIDALGO COSTA

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCE

HIGH SCHOOL TEACHER

CONSORCI BARCELONA

2022 - Present

Teach English language skills (reading, writing and speaking) to secondary and high school students. Prepare and adapt educational materials, evaluating academic progress. Foster an inclusive and motivating learning environment.

CUSTOMER SERVICE

FTT

2015-2022

Provide support and solutions to customer queries, ensuring customer satisfaction. Manage and resolve complaints efficiently. Maintain accurate and up-to-date records of customer interactions.

EDUCATION

BOOTCAMP FULL STACK DEVELOPER

GeeksHubs

2024

UNIVERSITY MASTER'S DEGREE IN EDUCATION AND ICT

Universitat Oberta de Catalunya, UOC

2024

UNIVERSITY MASTER'S DEGREE TEACHER TRAINING

Blanquerna, URL

2022

POSTGRADUATE EDUCATIONAL DIRECTION AND LEADERSHIP

Universitat Oberta de Catalunya, UOC

2021

DEGREE IN ENGLISH STUDIES

Universitat de Barcelona, UB 2015-2020

ERASMUS 2018-2019

PROJECTS

Back-end Project

JavaScript Logic Project

Interactive TV Project

Restaurant Menu Project